Paul Mellon Centre for Studies in British Art newsletters
Yale Center for British Art, Institutional Archives
Paul Mellon Centre for Studies in British Art newsletters
1995-12-2017-05
A007
Yale Center for British Art, Institutional Archives
.209
(1 box)
Paul Mellon Centre for Studies in British Art
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of the biannual newsletters for the Paul Mellon Centre for Studies in British Art from the charity's inaugural issue in December 1995 to May 2017.
Biographical / Historical
The Paul Mellon Centre for Studies in British Art, founded in 1970, is an educational charity committed to supporting original research into the history of British art and architecture of all periods. The Centre contains an extensive library and manuscript collection, with over 12,000 books about British art. It is the sister institution to the Yale Center for British Art, with which it collaborates closely, and is part of Yale University.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is unprocessed and may not be available for immediate access.
Art, British; Art -- Periodicals
- Paul Mellon Center for Studies in British Art Newsletters, January 1, 1995 - May 30, 2013; 1; (1 box)
  - Issue 1 December 1995, Jan 1, 1995 - May 30, 2013 (Box 905)
  - Issue 2 June 1996 (Box 905)
  - Issue 3 December 1996 (Box 905)
  - Issue 4 June 1997 (Box 905)
  - Issue 5 December 1997 (Box 905)
  - Issue 6 June 1998 (Box 905)
  - Issue 7 December 1998 (Box 905)
  - Issue 8 June 1999 (Box 905)
  - Issue 9 December 1999 (Box 905)
  - Issue 10 June 2000 (Box 905)
  - Issue 11 December 2000 (Box 905)
  - Issue 12 June 2001 (Box 905)
  - Issue 13 December 2001 (Box 905)
  - Issue 14 June 2002 (Box 905)
  - Issue 15 December 2002 (Box 905)
  - Issue 16 June 2003 (Box 905)
  - Issue 17 December 2003 (Box 905)
  - Issue 18 June 2004 (Box 905)
  - Issue 19 December 2004 (Box 905)
  - Issue 20 June 2005 (Box 905)
  - Issue 21 December 2005 (Box 905)
  - Issue 22 June 2006 (Box 905)
  - Issue 23 December 2006 (Box 905)
  - Issue 24 June 2007 (Box 905)
  - Issue 25 November 2007 (Box 905)
  - Issue 26 June 2008 (Box 905)
  - Issue 27 December 2008 (Box 905)
  - Issue 28 June 2009 (Box 905)
  - Issue 29 December 2009 (Box 905)
  - Issue 30 June 2010 (Box 905)
  - Issue 31 December 2010 (Box 905)
  - Issue 32 June 2011 (Box 905)
  - Issue 33 December 2011 (Box 905)
  - Issue 34 June 2012 (Box 905)
  - Issue 35 December 2012 (Box 905)
  - Issue 36 May 2013 (Box 905)
  - Issue 37 September 2013 (Box 905)
  - Issue 38 January 2014 (Box 905)
  - Issue 39 May 2014 (Box 905)